Akane, can you hear me?
I'm picking you up, okay?
The answer?
No.
Maybe his tutoring session is going overtime.
Yeah, but even still, it's not like him to just leave us in the dark.
Who knows, though? Maybe he's out with a girl.
I mean, how suspicious was that call he got the other day?
Yamada's not that kind of character.
You really don't get him, do you, Prez?
I'm telling you, if you don't stay on your toes and make your move soon, you're gonna lose him to some random girl.
I know that.
Hmm?
I know. So don't pressure me like that.
If it's tearing you up that badly inside, you might as well tell him how you feel.
What's even holding you back at this point?
One of these days, he'll meet someone.
I have a feeling that he will.
Excuse me, Yamada.
Do you know G.O.S.E.?
It's a popular FPS game.
You play it, right?
Last night around 10pm, you matched against me.
Do you remember?
In-game, I'm YTO3.
But my real name is Yukari Tsubaki, and I'm from Class D.
If it's alright with you, I'd like you to show me how you play.
But why?
I just have my reasons, that's why.
She totally thinks you cheated, bro.
Leave when you're done, okay?
Of course.
Hey, Tsubaki, you should watch my epic gameplay later, too.
The truth is, I was a little suspicious.
I didn't think anyone could play like that with sheer skill.
But I misjudged you.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Your skills are amazing.
Shouldn't you be playing professionally?
Just like how I met you then.
I know that one day,
you'll meet someone, too.
For someone with such arresting good lucks, he's quiet and reserved.
For someone who speaks so bluntly, he's actually pretty thoughtful.
Anybody who's good friends with him knows that well.
And also...
Yamada?
When we worked together on the committee last week, you were really a major help to me.
So I, uh...
Uh, have you and I ever spoken?
That you can be a little cruel.
Hey, did you hear Miss Shirai-shi from class D finally confessed her feelings to Yamada?
For real?
But of course she got shot down.
No way.
If Miss Shirai-shi can't get him, who can?
Maybe he's not into girls.
You think so?
Come on, that would be such a waste.
Right?
We're second years, and you still don't have a girlfriend.
If you stay single with your popularity, there are bound to be false rumors.
Why should I care what other people say?
It doesn't matter.
Oh, well, I get what you mean.
But I felt bad seeing people spread lies about you.
Don't you have a type?
Not really.
Surely even you must have some idea.
I don't.
Then who was your first crush-
I mean it.
There's no one.
He sighed.
Sorry about that.
Oh, no.
I am.
I shouldn't have pushed you like that.
I feel bad.
So, um...
Uh...
Um...
It's just...
Come to think of it.
Years ago, there was a girl who confessed that she liked me.
Back then, she got bullied like crazy.
Huh?
It got pretty bad, so she stopped coming to school.
But since I lived nearby, our teacher would send me to her house with handouts, and that's how we became friends.
However, when she did come to school, she said if I wasn't there, she felt like she didn't belong.
So I tried to stay by her side, so I tried to stay by her side as much as I could.
Then, are you saying that you liked that girl too, Yamada?
Akito...
Let's stay together forever, even after we're all grown up.
I can't promise you that.
I only did all that because our teacher told me to.
That's all there was to it.
The bullying never stopped, so she ended up transferring out.
Although, sometimes, I think of her.
The last time we spoke, I made her cry pretty hard.
And I have moments where I'm left wondering, what would have been the right thing to say.
But I still don't know.
And now, it seems like such a drag.
Since then, I've never been comfortable around girls.
I see.
The reality is, this guy doesn't have much interest in himself.
That would explain why he doesn't really notice when other people care about him.
Either that, or he's been deliberately averting his gaze from them.
And did he say it was a drag?
How scary.
I'd better make sure I don't fall for this guy.
If I ever fall in love with someone as cruel as him, I'll definitely be hurt someday.
I don't want that.
Order delivery.
Akane, can you drink some water?
Just try.
Even if it's a little bit.
She's burning up.
This fever, it's really bad.
Cold.
So cold.
I feel awful.
I'm so hot.
I'm cold.
What's going on?
Behind my eyes, my head is spinning.
I don't get it.
What's happening to me right now?
Akane.
Akane?
Where's your card for your health insurance?
Health insurance?
Insurance card.
And...
My bag.
Huh?
Hold on.
I could have sworn Yamada was just here.
Am I imagining things?
Miss Kinoshita?
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Why did it get...
So noisy around me?
Okay.
Huh?
What time...
Is it now?
Did I...
Fall asleep after that?
I guess I never made it to the store, did I?
On the bright side, though, I think I'm starting to feel a tiny bit better.
Huh?
Why?
Why is he...
It's cold.
Why are you here?
I see.
It's a dream.
I'm cold.
So you can stand on your feet again.
How are you feeling?
Huh?
A bit surprised.
I didn't mean it that way.
Wait!
It's not a dream!
Why are you here?
I mean, you can't catch this!
I'll explain it all to you in a moment, so go back to bed for now.
You couldn't even drink water.
You were in critical condition, you know.
Okay.
Okay...
How are you feeling now?
um actually when i woke up earlier i thought i was feeling a little better
well i'm really glad to hear that when i got here you had collapsed by the bike racks
did i really come to think of it i do remember thinking i saw someone that looked like yamada
that means it really was yamada who helped me but you seemed really sick so
did he come all the way here to check on me because he was worried
there's a chance he could have caught my cold himself but he stayed with me anyway
why would he go out of his way to be so nice to someone like me
thank you i'm so grateful yamada you don't know how exhausted i was
you really saved my life i mean it i have no idea how i'll ever repay you for this
you're an angel
yeah sure
anyway as i was saying
i'm so sorry for saying you were cold but really you're such a kind person
did she ever say that to me
the truth is you've always been kind from the moment
if you keep reaching over you'll fall
i'm sorry i stepped on it
oh yeah that book
i didn't have anything to do so i borrowed it and started reading
is a good book huh it totally saved me after the whole heartbreak thing you know
i didn't really get it
it's not exactly something you could relate to
since i'm pretty sure you're the side who does the dumping yamada
no i wouldn't say that
oh come on now
this illness really has you keyed up and scary
well i'm sure the emotional strain is tough for the dumpers too
but you're especially kind so it'd be really draining
i'm not
i'm not the good guy you think i am
at all
that's the same look takuma gave me
like he was sorry and in pain
and like he wished he could just disappear
but it's all right though
i'm okay with it
that's romance
even though he cheated on you
well
now that it's in the past
sometimes i'm glad he was up front about dumping me
instead of keeping up a lie
sorry akane
at least i ended up not having to feel truly humiliated
sorry
i knew nothing i said would change his mind
so to make it easier
i just accepted the breakup right away
okay
someday
when i've become a memory he looks back on
i'd rather he remembered me with a smile on my face
instead of frowning and all teary-eyed
i want him to think of me like
i really shouldn't have let her go
she was great
that's a lot better don't you think
did you feel
sorry for me
goodbye
akito
i'm sorry
but you were always there for me
so thank you
take care
goodbye
i guess that's right
did it go down
yeah
yeah i think it did a little
yamada
is it okay if i eat some of that yogurt you bought earlier
yeah sure
are those tears of joy or
it's tasty but it kills to swallow
oh
if it was anyone other than yamada sitting there when i woke up
i would have definitely had a panic attack
but what's this vibe he's giving off
for some reason i feel so safe and secure
well i bet it must have been an ordeal for him
he's uncomfortable around women as it is
thanks for the yogurt
could you put this on the table
sure
oh crap
huh
hey
my leg
what
i'm getting a cramp
cramp
stretch your leg out
you've gotta stretch it
jeez
akane
here
give me your leg
it hurts
wait stop
no no no
that's too much
it hurts
kick your hands off of me
please
stop moving
hang in there
it hurts
the hurt
he's just
so mad
the pain went away
better
i thought i was gonna die
that's an exaggeration
i'm telling you
it was killing me
what's this
seems like
he's totally looking at me
but why
wait
what's going on
i felt so safe and relaxed
but
what was
making me feel that way
what i didn't move away
no reason
stop laughing at me
it's not what you think
it's not alright
anyway
like
we can do it
oh
i Spirit
let me show you
it
I don't know
how old
rep
I'm going to make you
ok
It's not all right!
Okay, I'm off.
You're going to school without sleeping?
Yeah, I'm used to it.
I really am sorry about this.
If you start feeling sick, let me know, okay?
And by the way, thanks for taking me to the hospital and everything.
I'll be sure to thank you properly another time.
I really didn't do much.
So please don't worry about it.
They said to wait a day and see how you feel.
Didn't come get looked at again during regular office hours.
So remember to do that.
Okay, I'll remember.
It seems at night they can't do those really detailed tests.
Well, since you did get a lot better after the IV,
I guess they just want to be sure.
Thanks for having me.
Sorry.
I didn't realize you were standing right there.
No, that's my bad.
I got a little too close.
It's almost like my body's being drawn to him of its own accord.
Akane, your hand.
I have to leave.
I'm sorry.
Don't mind me.
Please go.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm all good.
So please go.
Hey, I know.
When I'm done at the hospital, should I let you know how it went?
No, I'm sure it's just a cold.
What?
Oh, sorry.
No, that's silly.
You know, I just sort of thought that I might have given my cold to you.
I wasn't sure if you were like worried about it or anything.
So I was just checking is all.
Then please let me know.
Okay.
Take care.
Hey.